

SUMMARY

Hasyin Iqbal Mun

+4917632268549



hasyinmini@gmail.com



Heidelberg, Germany

Previously worked as a Copywriter at an event management agency. Skillfully manages multiple tasks and meets tight deadlines in high-pressure environments. Great team player with average leadership skills. Committed to quality performance with an ability to learn quickly. Also a person who pays attention to the smallest of he details and adapt in a fast-speed environment. Always hungry to learn.

CAREER

AUG 2020 - PRESENT

DECATHLON

Decathlon Deutschland

LOGISTICS SPECIALIST

- As a logistics employee, it is highly important to re-think the processes every day. Together with a strong team, my responsibilities include:
- Picking, sorting and packing goods.
- The timely delivery to the Decathlon branches in South Germany
- The maintenance and inventory of stocks
- To plan and implement projects independently

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT



UpWork

CONSULTANT - FREELANCER

- Write for webpages, blogs and potentially for social media, e-books, slogans, and video script.
- Work with creative clients to ensure that the visual elements of the webpage complement the words.

JAN 2018 - JAN 2019



Venuescape, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

JUNIOR COPYWRITER

- Responsible for handling the social media assets of the company.
- Brainstorming visual and copy ideas with other members of the creative team.
- Presenting initial ideas to the creative director, some of which may be developed into workable concepts

EDUCATION

SEPT 2019- OCT 2020



Schiller International University, Heidelberg

MASTERS OF INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS

 An exciting Dual Master's Degree Program with University of Roehampton to achieve personal goals, regardless of specific career goals.

JAN 2015- NOV 2018



INTI International University, Malaysia

BACHELORS OF MEDIA AND MASS COMMUNICATIONS

- Major in Public Relations.
- Exposure to various areas of the media and marketing industries through Dual Award Bachelor (Honours) degree program with the University of Hertfordshire in Mass Communications.

HONOURS & AWARDS

FEBRUARY 2020



MainMUN 2020

GOETHE-UNIVERSITÄT FRANKFURT AM MAIN

 Participated in the Main Model United Nations conference and contributed to realizing a simulation of United Nations and other international organizations. Represented as the Press Agency of China Daily, while developing skills in article writing, academic researching and networking.

SKILLS

- MS Word
- Adobe PhotoShop
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- MS PowerPoint

- Social Media Communications
- Email Marketing
- Analytical Skills
- Creative Writing